<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Welcome on Takahē</title><link>https://jointakahe.org/</link><description>Recent content in Welcome on Takahē</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 19 Nov 2022 08:51:26 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jointakahe.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Welcome</title><link>https://jointakahe.org/posts/welcome/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Nov 2022 08:51:26 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://jointakahe.org/posts/welcome/</guid><description>Hello!</description></item><item><title>Code of Conduct</title><link>https://jointakahe.org/conduct/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jointakahe.org/conduct/</guid><description>This code of conduct applies to all spaces managed by the Takahē project. This includes GitHub issues and discussions, Discord, takahe.social, and other forums where the project may participate. In addition, violations of this code outside these spaces may affect a person&amp;rsquo;s ability to participate within them.
If you believe someone is violating the code of conduct, we ask that you report it by emailing conduct@jointakahe.org.
Be friendly and patient. Be welcoming.</description></item><item><title>Custom Domains Guide</title><link>https://jointakahe.org/guides/custom-domains/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jointakahe.org/guides/custom-domains/</guid><description>So you want to point a custom domain at takahe.social? Great! Before you start, you need to understand a few things:
Custom domains are limited to only our Featured Supporter Patreon Tier or higher, those who donate an equivalent monthly amount via direct invoice, or for open-source project or charities (email contact@jointakahe.org for information about those options).
Once you make accounts (identities) on your custom domain, you will not be able to move them away from takahe.</description></item><item><title>Privacy Policy</title><link>https://jointakahe.org/privacy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jointakahe.org/privacy/</guid><description>Last updated December 16, 2022
This privacy notice for Scaled Industries, Ltd. (&amp;ldquo;Company,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;we,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;us,&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;our&amp;rdquo;), describes how and why we might collect, store, use, and/or share (&amp;ldquo;process&amp;rdquo;) your information when you use our services (&amp;ldquo;Services&amp;rdquo;), such as when you:
Visit our websites at https://takahe.social, https://jointakahe.org, or any website of ours that links to this privacy notice Engage with us in other related ways, including any sales, marketing, or events Questions or concerns?</description></item><item><title>Supporters</title><link>https://jointakahe.org/supporters/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jointakahe.org/supporters/</guid><description>These supporters have generously donated to Takahē, either directly or via our Patreon!
Featured Supporters Jamie Matthews Supporters Brian Grohe Josh Simmons Mark McKeague Naldela Isur&amp;rsquo;Ra Teleyal Shuuji Takahashi The Doodle Project Tyler Kennedy (tktech)</description></item><item><title>Takahē 0.9 Timeline Removal</title><link>https://jointakahe.org/guides/timeline-removal/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jointakahe.org/guides/timeline-removal/</guid><description>In an upcoming release of Takahē, we are removing the timeline, compose, and explore views from the Web UI; instead, we will be focusing on the app API and ensuring compatibility with a large range of Mastodon client applications.
If you do not use the web UI currently, there is nothing to do; everything will continue to work, and you&amp;rsquo;ll just see a new UI if you log in to change your settings.</description></item><item><title>takahe.social</title><link>https://jointakahe.org/takahesocial/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jointakahe.org/takahesocial/</guid><description>takahe.social is our &amp;ldquo;flagship&amp;rdquo; server - a Takahē server run by the main developers as a testbed and proving ground for server changes, and a place to get user feedback.
Much like Takahē itself, it is still in development - we don&amp;rsquo;t encourage you to rely on it for anything serious. It mostly works, but there&amp;rsquo;s lots of sharp edges and things that aren&amp;rsquo;t quite fully done yet.
Joining The server is open for signups up to an internal user cap.</description></item><item><title>Terms of Service</title><link>https://jointakahe.org/terms/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jointakahe.org/terms/</guid><description>Last updated December 16, 2022
TABLE OF CONTENTS
AGREEMENT TO TERMS INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY RIGHTS USER REPRESENTATIONS USER REGISTRATION PROHIBITED ACTIVITIES USER GENERATED CONTRIBUTIONS CONTRIBUTION LICENSE SOCIAL MEDIA SUBMISSIONS THIRD-PARTY WEBSITE AND CONTENT SITE MANAGEMENT PRIVACY POLICY DIGITAL MILLENNIUM COPYRIGHT ACT (DMCA) NOTICE AND POLICY TERM AND TERMINATION MODIFICATIONS AND INTERRUPTIONS GOVERNING LAW DISPUTE RESOLUTION CORRECTIONS DISCLAIMER LIMITATIONS OF LIABILITY INDEMNIFICATION USER DATA ELECTRONIC COMMUNICATIONS, TRANSACTIONS, AND SIGNATURES CALIFORNIA USERS AND RESIDENTS MISCELLANEOUS CONTACT US 1.</description></item></channel></rss>